Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  - Post War House, 1950-1959
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 66)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 66)
  - Pottery Barn
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 66)
  - Enoch Pratt Free Library
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 67)
    - Drawings (Box 66–67, Box 216)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 67)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 67)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 66–67, Box 216)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 66–67, Box 216)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 66–67, Box 216)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
  - Pratt, Charles
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 67)
  - Preston, Hart, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 67)
    - Drawings (Box 67)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 67)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 67)
    - Material Samples (Box 67)
  - J. Press Store
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 68)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 68)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 68)
  - Princeton University, 1964
    Job location: Princeton, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Box 68, Box 266)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 68, Box 266)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 68, Box 266)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 68)
    - Photographs (Box 68)
  - Progressive Synagogue, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 68)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 68)
  - Public Service of New Jersey, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Box 68)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 68)
  - Publishers Clearing House, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Box 68)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 68)
  - Queens College, 1958
    Job location: Queens, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 68)
    - Drawings (Box 68)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 68)
  - R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company
    Job location: Winston-Salem, NC
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69, Box 273)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 69, Box 273)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 69, Box 273)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 273)
  - Rahv, Nathalie Residence, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 69)
    - Material Samples (Box 69)
  - Raymond Loewy Associates, 1946
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
  - Raymond and Rado, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
  - Readers Digest Building, 1950
    Job location: Tokyo, Japan
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 69)
  - Reeves Residence, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
  - Republic National Bank
    - Drawings (Box 310)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 310)
  - Restaurant Associates, Inc., Restaurant, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 69)
  - Revlon, Inc., 1959
    - Drawings (Box 387)
  - Revlon, Salon
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
  - Reyburn Plaza, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 69)
  - Reynolds Metal Company
    Job location: Richmond, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 69)
  - Reznikoff Residence, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 321)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 321)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 321)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 321)
    - Photographs (Box 69)
  - Rhode Island School of Design
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 69)
  - Richards Center, 1977
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 69)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 69)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 69)
  - Ring Residence, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
  - Rio Gas Station
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
  - Riverside Church, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 70)
    - Drawings (Box 70, Box 148)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 70)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 70)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 70, Box 148)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 70, Box 148)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 70)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 148)
  - Rizzoli Editore ( See Also: Gotham Development Corporation), 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 70)
    - Drawings (Box 70, Box 224, Box 236, Box 295)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 70, Box 130)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 70, Box 130, Box 236)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 70, Box 130, Box 236)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 70, Box 224)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 70, Box 224, Box 295)
    - Photographs (Box 70)
  - Robbins House, 1954
    Job location: Toledo, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 70)
    - Drawings (Box 70)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 70)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 70)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 70)
  - Rock Creek Plaza, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 71)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 71)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 71)
  - Rockefeller House, 1956
    Job location: Tarrytown, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 71)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 71)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson Lodge, 1959
    Job location: Pocantico Hills, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71, Box 288)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 71, Box 288)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 71)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 71)
  - Rockefeller, John D. III Sculpture Lighting, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Photographs (Box 71)
  - Rock-Time Building, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
  - Rogers Building, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 71)
  - Rogers, Will Equestrian Statue
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 71)
  - Room 313, Executive Office Building
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano Memorial
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 71)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 71)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 71)
  - Roosevelt Hotel, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 72)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 72)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 72)
    - Photographs (Box 72)
  - Rosedown Plantation
    Job location: St. Francisville, LA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 220)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 220)
    - Photographs (Box 72)
  - Rosengarten, Frederic Residence, 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 72)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 72)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 72)
  - Rosenthal, Richard Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 72)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 72)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 72)
  - Rosenthal Shop
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 72)
  - Royal Bank of Canada (See Also: Place Ville Marie), 1962
    Job location: Montreal, Canada
    Collaborator: I.M. Pei & Associates
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 65, Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 65, Box 72, Box 164, Box 168, Box 298)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 298)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 298)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 298)
  - Roxy Theater
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 72)
    - Drawings (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 72)
    - Photographs (Box 72)
  - Rubin, Joseph Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
    - Drawings (Box 73)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 73)
  - Rutgers University (Art Museum), 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 73)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 73)
  - Rutgers University (Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, Voorhees Hall), 1964
    Job location: New Brunswick, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73, Box 406)
    - Drawings (Box 73)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 73)
  - Sacred Heart Dominican College, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
  - Salisbury, Charles Residence, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73, Box 406)
    - Drawings (Box 73, Box 237)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 237, Box 406)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 237)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 73, Box 237)
  - San Diego Fine Arts Gallery (See also: Timken Fine Arts Gallery), 1962
    Job location: San Diego, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
    - Drawings (Box 73, Box 131, Box 143, Box 163, Box 240, Box 272)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 163, Box 272)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 163)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 73, Box 143, Box 272)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 73, Box 143, Box 163, Box 272)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 73, Box 143)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 131, Box 163)
  - San Diego Theater and Arts Foundation, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1960
    Job location: Bronxville, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
  - Saturday Evening Post Interview, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 73)
  - Savoy Plaza Hotel, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
  - Schaefer, Bertha, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 74)
  - Scheuer, Walter Apartment, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 74)
  - Scheuer, Walter Office, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 74)
  - Schlumberger Well Surveying Corporation, 1953
    Job location: Ridgefield, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 74, Box 406)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 74)
  - School at 145 East 75th Street, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 74)
  - Kane Schwartz Enterprises
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
  - Scientific Resources, Inc., 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 74)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 74)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 74)
  - Seagram Building, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Drawings (Box 74, Box 105–106, Box 108, Box 338, Box 373)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 74)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 105, Box 108, Box 338, Box 373)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 74, Box 106, Box 108, Box 406)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 105)
    - Photographs (Box 406)
  - Seagram Building, Barber Shop, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
  - Seagram Building, Brasserie Extension, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 74)
    - Photographs (Box 74)
  - Seagram Building, Four Seasons Restaurant, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75, Box 406)
    - Drawings (Box 106)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 106, Box 396–399, Box 406)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 106)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 399)
    - Photographs (Box 75, Box 406)
  - Seal Harbor Museum
    Job location: Seal Harbor, ME
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
    - Drawings (Box 75)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 387)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 75)
  - Second Church of Christ Scientist
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75, Box 407)
    - Drawings (Box 75, Box 231, Box 407)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 407)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 75, Box 231, Box 407)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 231, Box 407)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 75, Box 231)
    - Material Samples (Box 407)
  - Seiden Apartment, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
    - Drawings (Box 75)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 75)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 75)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 75)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 75)
  - Selig Residence, 1957
    Job location: New Rochelle, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
    - Photographs (Box 75)
  - Seligman, Robert Residence, 1946
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
    - Drawings (Box 75, Box 387)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 75, Box 387)
  - Seltzer, Sidney Apartment, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
    - Drawings (Box 155, Box 237)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 237)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 155)
  - Seton Hill, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
  - Seventeen Magazine Reception Room, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 75)
  - Sheldon Art Gallery, 1962
    Job location: Lincoln, NE
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Drawings (Box 76, Box 156, Box 174, Box 381)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 76, Box 156, Box 174, Box 381)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 76, Box 156, Box 174, Box 381)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 76, Box 174)
    - Photographs (Box 76)
  - Sheldon Quadrangle, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
  - Sherwood, Thorne House
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Photographs (Box 76)
  - Shield of Big Emblem
    - Drawings (Box 142)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 142)
  - Shoshany, Edmond Residence, 1975
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Drawings (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 76)
  - Sibley's, 1968
    Job location: Syracuse, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 407)
    - Photographs (Box 407)
  - Silvray Lighting, Inc., 1958
    Job location: Radio City, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 76)
  - Simes Company, 1962
    Job location: College Point, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Drawings (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 76, Box 387)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 76)
  - Simmons Fastener Corporation, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Drawings (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 76)
  - Simpson's Victorian Restaurant, 400 East 57th Street
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 76)
    - Drawings (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 76)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 76)
    - Photographs (Box 76)
  - Singer & Sons, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
    - Photographs (Box 77)
  - Singer, Herbert Apartment, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 77, Box 155)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 77, Box 155)
    - Photographs (Box 77)
  - Skidmore, Owings and Merrill, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
  - Slick, Tom House, 1958
    Job location: San Antonio, TX
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
  - Sloan, Arthur Apartment, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
  - Sloane Hotel, 1970
    Job location: Knightsbridge, London
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 77)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 77)
  - Smith, Hinchman and Grylls Associates Inc., 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
  - Smith, Solomon B. Residence, 1963
    Job location: Lake Forest, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 387)
  - Soby, James Thrall House
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 77)
  - Societe Anonyme du Gaz, 1956
    - Drawings (Box 282)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 282)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 282)
  - Socony Mobile Oil Company, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
  - Solinger, David Apartment, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
  - Sonnabend, Roger, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
    - Drawings (Box 77, Box 387)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 77)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 77)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 77, Box 387)
  - Sonotone Corporation
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 77)
  - Sons et Lumeire, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 78)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1962
    Job location: Edwardsville, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78, Box 249)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 249)
    - Photographs (Box 78)
  - Spectacle, Son et Lumiere
    - Unidentified Material (Box 9)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Photographs (Box 60)
  - Spivack House
    - Unidentified Material (Box 360)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 360)
    - Drawings (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 360)
  - Spring Mills, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 78)
  - Squaw Valley Inn, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78, Box 135)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 78, Box 135)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 135)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 135)
  - St. Bernard's School, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 237)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 237)
  - St. Louis Municipal Opera Association, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
  - St. Michaels College, Chapel, 1963
    Job location: Winooski Park, Burlington, VT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78, Box 141, Box 150, Box 211, Box 222, Box 285)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 78, Box 141, Box 211, Box 222)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 141, Box 211)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 78, Box 141, Box 150, Box 211, Box 222, Box 285)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 141, Box 150, Box 211, Box 222, Box 285)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 141, Box 211)
    - Photographs (Box 285)
  - St. Regis Hotel
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 78)
  - St. Stephens Episcopal New Harmony Church, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 78)
  - St. Thomas University, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
    - Drawings (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 78)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 78, Box 387)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 78, Box 387)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 78)
  - Stardust Hotel, 1960
    Job location: Easter Isle
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 78)
  - Stardust Hotel, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 79, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 79)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 155)
  - State Capitol Grounds
    - Drawings (Box 159)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 159)
  - State House, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 145)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 145)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 145)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 145)
  - State Museum of Archives, Art, State, and Natural History, 1950
    Job location: North Carolina
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 79)